Finding Aid for the The James D. Squires Papers
Special Collections and University Archives
James D. Squires Papers
Inclusive: 1955-2004; Bulk: 1981-2002
undated
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0588
31.1 linear_feet
The James D. Squires (1943-) papers were donated to Vanderbilt University by Squires in 2005, and encompass his careers as a journalist and editor, as a political adviser and as an author. The Nashville native graduated from Peabody College in 1966 and started his journalism career at the Tennessean. He now breeds thoroughbred horses—including 2001 Kentucky Derby winner Monarchos—at his farm in Kentucky.
Biographical Note
Born in Tennessee on April 3, 1943, James D. Squires rose from mill worker’s son to editor and executive vice president of one of the country’s most influential newspapers, the Chicago Tribune. Squires is the grandson of Dave White, a member of Garner Robinson’s “Old Hickory Gang” of freewheeling Nashville politicians in the mid-twentieth century, about whom Squires wrote The Secrets of the Hopewell Box in 1996. A 1966 Peabody College graduate, Squires began his journalism career at the Tennessean in 1962, where he worked as a reporter, Washington correspondent and night city desk editor before moving to the Tribune in 1972. The 1970-71 Harvard Nieman Foundation for Journalism fellow worked in the Washington bureau until 1977, becoming the bureau chief in 1974. While at the Tribune, Squires covered Watergate, presidential elections and accompanied former President Gerald Ford on a 1975 state visit to China.
Squires moved from the Tribune to Tribune Company’s Orlando Sentinel-Star (later the Orlando Sentinel) in 1977, where he was editor until returning to Chicago as editor of the Tribune in 1981. Eight-and-a-half years and seven Pulitzers for the Tribune later, Squires resigned. He and his wife Mary Anne moved to a horse farm in Kentucky, where he bred 2001 Kentucky Derby winner Monarchos. He was an adjunct professor at Harvard University in 1990 and Middle Tennessee State University in 1992. Squires was Ross Perot’s media adviser in 1992.
He has written three books, contributed to one and edited another. Squires has two adult children.
Books:
A Search for Justice with John Seigenthaler (1971)
The American Millstone (edited) by Chicago Tribune staff (1986)
Read All About It! The Corporate Takeover of America’s Newspapers (1993)
The Secrets of the Hopewell Box: Stolen Elections, Southern Politics, and a City’s Coming of Age (1996)
Horse of a Different Color: A Tale of Breeding Geniuses, Dominant Females, and the Fastest Derby Winner Since Secretariat (2002)
Scope and Content Note
The collection contains six series, encompassing James Squires’ careers as a journalist and editor, political adviser, author and university professor, and was donated to Vanderbilt University by Squires in 2005.
The materials in the collection include correspondence, newspaper clippings, photographs, videocassettes, audiocassettes and signed original political cartoons. Several books, including copies of Squires’ published works, were part of the original collection but have been removed and shelved with the Sevier and Southern Civilization collections. Roughly half the journalism correspondence is made up of letters to the editor. These are arranged chronologically rather than alphabetically because of the topical nature of the letters. Additionally, many newspaper articles and faxes have been photocopied for preservation; the originals are located at the end of the appropriate series or subseries and are arranged chronologically. Any photographs included with correspondence have also been photocopied and the originals placed with the other photographs in each series or subseries.
The 63 boxes of the collection have been arranged in the following six series: journalism career, Ross Perot campaign, books, university courses, biographical material with miscellaneous correspondence and writings, and multimedia and oversized material.
- Series I: Journalism career (1972-1989)
  - The Tennessean (1962-1972)
    - Box 1: Correspondence, notes, clippings
      - Incoming correspondence - Ellis, Craig-Woods, Frank (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Notes (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Notebooks, 1-4 (Box 1, Folder 3)
        1 [1965-1966] Howard Baker
        2 1971 Elton Hayes’ killing by Memphis police officers
        3 [1971] Gambling in Tennessee
        4 1972 Democratic presidential candidate Fred Harris
      - Notebooks, 5-8 (Box 1, Folder 4)
        5 1972 Democratic presidential candidate Hubert Humphrey
        6 1972 Democratic presidential candidates Scoop Jackson and Julian Bond
        7 1972 Democratic presidential campaign notes
        8 1972 Tennessee Democratic convention
      - Notebooks, 9-11; 9 1972 Democratic campaign - Richard Daley and George McGovern 10 [1972] Prison reform 11 1974 Nixon opens new Grand Ole Opry off Briley Parkway (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Clippings, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Clippings, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Clippings, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Clippings, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Clippings, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Clippings, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Clippings, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Clippings, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Clippings, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Box 2: Clippings, press releases, certificate, photographs, original clippings
      - Clippings, January 9, 1972-March 19, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Clippings, April 3, 1972-May 21, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Clippings, June 11, 1972-August 20, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Clippings - n.d., 1972 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Clippings - n.d. (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Clippings - n.d. (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Clippings - n.d. (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Press releases (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Nieman Fellowship acceptance certificate (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Photographs (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Original clippings, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Original clippings, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Original clippings, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Original clippings, 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Original clippings, January 9, 1972-March 19, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Original clippings, April 3, 1972-May 21, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Original clippings, June 11, 1972-August 20, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Original clippings, n.d. 1972 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Original clippings, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Original clippings, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Chicago Tribune - Washington, D.C., (1972-1976)
    - Box 3: Correspondence, notes, byline files, clippings
      - Incoming correspondence - Angleton, James-Duscha, Julius (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Incoming correspondence - Hawley, Ed (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Incoming correspondence - Kennedy, Ethel-Patterson, Harriet (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Incoming correspondence - Simon, Paul-Stewart, Donald (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Incoming correspondence - Tankersley, Tiffany-Woods, Frank A.; unidentified (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Outgoing correspondence, 1974-February 28, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Outgoing correspondence, March 1975-December 1975 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - xOutgoing correspondence, 1976; n.d. (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Notebooks, 1-4 (Box 3, Folder 9)
        1 1973 Watergate - James McCord testimony
        2 [1973-1974] Watergate
        3 1975 Announcement of U.S. troop withdrawal from Vietnam
        4 1975 Gerald Ford’s St. Patrick’s Day speech at Notre Dame University
      - Notebooks, 5-8 (Box 3, Folder 10)
        5 1975 Edward Kennedy
        6 [1975-1976] Republican campaign
        7 February 1976 George Wallace rally at Lithuanian Hall, South Boston; New Hampshire presidential primary
        8 February 1976 Massachusetts presidential primary
      - Notebooks, 6-12 (Box 3, Folder 11)
        9 March 1976 Florida presidential primary
        10 April 1976 Pennsylvania presidential primary
        11 April 1976 Pennsylvania presidential primary
        12 1976 Democratic presidential primary campaign
      - Notebooks, 13-16 (Box 3, Folder 12)
        13 1976 Democratic presidential primary campaign; Virginia Washington Stith
        14 1976 Republican presidential primary campaign
        15 1976 Republican presidential primary campaign
        16 1976 Republican presidential primary campaign
    - Box 4: Notebooks, notes, byline files
      - Notebooks, 17-20 (Box 4, Folder 1)
        17 August 1976 Republican National Convention
        18 August 1976 Republican National Convention
        19 October 1976 notes for October 17, 1976 story “A Candidate Whose Appeal is Regional”
        20 1977 editorial notes
      - Notes, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Notes, 1976 Republican National Convention (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Notes, 1976 Republican National Convention (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Byline file, October 1972-December 1972 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Byline file, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Byline file, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Byline file, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Byline file, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Box 5: Byline files, clippings by others
      - Byline file, November 21, 1975-December 8, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Byline file, 1975 columns (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Byline file, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Byline file, 1976 columns (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Byline file, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Clippings, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Clippings, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Clippings, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Clippings, August 15, 1976-August 16, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Clippings, August 17, 1976-August 19, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Clippings, August 20, 1976-November 4, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Press releases, July 1976 (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Press releases, August 1976; n.d. (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Box 6: Telex and wires, corrections, publications
      - Telexed stories, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Telexed stories, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Telexed/wired stories, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Wire reports, January 1974 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Wire reports, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Wire reports, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Story corrections (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Publications, Battleline July 1976 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Publications, The Bulletin July/August 1974 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Publications, Congressional Quarterly Special Report: Guide to the Republican National Convention 1976 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Publications, Focus July 1976 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Publications, Kansas City Media Information Guide RNC 1976 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Publications, Little Trib June 1974 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Publications, Political Intelligence 2(21) 1976 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Publications, A Report to the Senate Foreign Relations Committee and the House International Relations Committee by the Seventh Congressional Delegation to the People’s Republic of China October 28, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Publications, Time February 24, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Publications, Transmittal of Documents from the National Security Council to the Chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff—Committee on Armed Services February 6, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Publications, Understanding China by Clayton Kirkpatrick, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Senate Armed Services Committee statement, Charles Radford, February 19, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Senate Armed Services Committee statement, Rear Admiral Robert O. Welander, February 21, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Miscellaneous, 1975 (China trip with Pres. Gerald Ford) (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Miscellaneous, 1976 (Republican National Convention) (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Miscellaneous, 1976 (Republican National Convention) (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - Miscellaneous, Hal Phillip Walker’s Platform (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - Miscellaneous, Environmental Defense Fund Staff Directory (Box 6, Folder 25)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - Photographs (Box 6, Folder 27)
      - Clippings - originals (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Orlando Sentinel (1977-1981)
    - Box 7: Incoming correspondence and letters to the editor
      - Incoming correspondence - Argirion, Michael-Driscoll, George C. (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Incoming correspondence - Eagles, Dana Scott-Huskey, C. Everette (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Incoming correspondence - Jean, Charlie-Liddon, W.M. (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Incoming correspondence - Madigan, John W.-Prague, Ellen (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Incoming correspondence - Reagan, Ronald-Twombly, Angus (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Incoming correspondence - Walker, Mort-Wurfel, Walt (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Incoming correspondence - Unidentified (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Letters to editor, February 1, 1977-February 11, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Letters to editor, February 12, 1977-February 28, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Letters to editor, March 1977 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Letters to editor, April 1977 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Letters to editor, May 1977 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Letters to editor, June 1977 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Letters to editor, July 1977 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Letters to editor, August 1977 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Box 8: Letters to the editor, outgoing correspondence, press releases
      - Letters to editor, September 1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Letters to editor, October 1977 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Letters to editor, November 1977 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Letters to editor, December 1977 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Letters to editor, January 1978 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Letters to editor, February 1978-April 1978 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Letters to editor, May 1978-June 1978 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Letters to editor, July 1978-August 1978 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Letters to editor, September 1978-December 1978 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Letters to editor, January 1979 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Letters to editor, February 1979 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Letters to editor, March 1979-August 1979 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Letters to editor, October 1979-December 1979 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - Letters to editor, April 1980-August 1980 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Letters to editor, September 1980-December 1980 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Letters to editor, January 1981-March 1981 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Letters to editor, April 1981-July 1981 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Letters to editor - n.d., signed (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - Letters to editor - n.d., unidentified (Box 8, Folder 19)
      - Outgoing correspondence, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 20)
      - Outgoing correspondence, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 21)
      - Outgoing correspondence, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 22)
      - Press releases (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Box 9: Clippings, publications, photographs, miscellaneous
      - Byline file, December 10, 1976-June 28, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Byline file, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Byline file, January 1978-April 1978 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Byline file, May 1978-August 1978 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Byline file, September 1978-December 1978 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Byline file, January 1979-March 1979 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Byline file, April 1979-July 1979 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Byline file, August 1979-December 1979 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Clippings, 1981; n.d. (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Publications, The Bulletin February 1977 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Publications, Florida Bar News January 10, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Publications, Sentinel-Star Galley Proof January 1, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Photographs (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Chicago Tribune - Chicago (1981-1989)
    - Box 10: Incoming correspondence
      - Incoming correspondence - Alexander, Bill-Axelrod, David (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Incoming correspondence - Bacon, Warren-Bazán, Dominator Kaiser (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Incoming correspondence - Bell, Gene-Brown, William (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Incoming correspondence - Brumback, Charles T. (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Incoming correspondence - Burleigh, William-Byrne, Jane (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Incoming correspondence - Cahill, Daniel-Carter, Jimmy and Rosalynn (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Incoming correspondence - Chapman, Steve-Christopher, Robert (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Incoming correspondence - Clark, Bill-Compton, James (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Incoming correspondence - Cook, Stanton (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Incoming correspondence - Coreth, Clemens-Curley, John (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Incoming correspondence - Daley, Steve-Dickey, Robert (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Incoming correspondence - Dishon, Colleen (Koky) (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Incoming correspondence - Dixon, Alan-Driscoll, John (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Incoming correspondence - Dubinin, Yuri-Dusseault, Norman (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Box 11: Incoming correspondence
      - Incoming correspondence - Egel, Marian-Fox-Alston, Jeanne (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Incoming correspondence - Frandsen, M. Olaf-Gore, Tipper (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Incoming correspondence - Gosselin, Denis-Hawley, Willis (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Incoming correspondence - Hay, Howard-Healy, Paul (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Incoming correspondence - Heck, Charles (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Incoming correspondence - Heffron, Mary-Huntington, John (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Incoming correspondence - Isaacs, Norman-Judge, Bernie (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Incoming correspondence - Kariher, Harry-Kirk, Don (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Incoming correspondence - Kirkpatrick, Clayton (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Incoming correspondence - Kirschner, Collette (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Incoming correspondence - Kleiman, Carol-Kovach, Bill (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Incoming correspondence - Lacy, Bill-Lehman, Tenney (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Incoming correspondence - Leonard, Dick (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Box 12: Incoming correspondence
      - Incoming correspondence - Letizia, Daniel-MacNelly, Jeff (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Incoming correspondence - Madigan, John (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Incoming correspondence - Mahoney, Barbara Ann-Miller, Arthur (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Incoming correspondence - Miller, Kristie-Mulroy, Thomas (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Incoming correspondence - Murphy, Pat-Murray, Randolph (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Incoming correspondence - Neal, Steve-Owens, Major (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Incoming correspondence - Page, Robert-Price, Michael (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Incoming correspondence - Quaal, Ward-Rice, William (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Incoming correspondence - Rider, Marsha (for Larry Flynt) (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Incoming correspondence - Risser, James-Seigenthaler, John (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Incoming correspondence - Senese, Diane-Simon, Paul (U.S. Senator) (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Incoming correspondence - Simon, Roger-Soeteber, Ellen (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Box 13: Incoming correspondence, memoranda, letters to the editor
      - Incoming correspondence - Soo, Charlie-Szczech, Bernadette (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Incoming correspondence - Taylor, Kristin-Trohan, Walter (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Incoming correspondence - Troutman, Russell (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Incoming correspondence - Trudeau, Garry-Vogt, Amanda (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Incoming correspondence - Waller, Michael-Wilson, James (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Incoming correspondence - Wilson, Jean (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Incoming correspondence - Wilson, Julie-Worthington, Rogers (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Incoming correspondence - Wright, Helen (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Incoming correspondence - Wood, Thomas-Zyda, Joan (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Incoming correspondence - Unidentified (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Memoranda (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Letters to editor, February 1982 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Letters to editor, October 1982 (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Letters to editor, January 1983-February 1983 (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Letters to editor, March 9, 1983-March 21, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Letters to editor, March 22, 1983-March 27, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Letters to editor, March 28, 1983-March 31, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Letters to editor, April 2, 1983-April 10, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Box 14: Letters to the editor
      - Letters to editor, April 11, 1983-April 14, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Letters to editor, April 15, 1983-April 26, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Letters to editor, May 1983-September 1983 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Letters to editor, October 1983-December 1983 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Letters to editor, n.d. [1983] (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Letters to editor, January 1984 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Letters to editor, February 1984 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Letters to editor, March 1984-August 1984 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Letters to editor, September 1984-October 1984 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Letters to editor, November 1984-December 1984; n.d. [1984] (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Letters to editor, January 1985-June 1985 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Letters to editor, July 1985 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Letters to editor, August 1985-November 1985 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - Letters to editor, December 1985 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - Letters to editor, Petition from North Lawndale residents, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Letters to editor, January 1986 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - Letters to editor, March 1986 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - Letters to editor, April 1986-December 1986 (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - Letters to editor, n.d. [1986] (Box 14, Folder 19)
      - Letters to editor, January 1987-April 1987 (Box 14, Folder 20)
      - Letters to editor, May 1987-July 1987 (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - Letters to editor, August 1987-December 1987 (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - Letters to editor, n.d. [1987] (Box 14, Folder 23)
      - Letters to editor, January 1988-April 1988 (Box 14, Folder 24)
      - Letters to editor, May 1988 (Box 14, Folder 25)
      - Letters to editor, June 1988-August 1988 (Box 14, Folder 26)
      - Letters to editor, January 1989 (Box 14, Folder 27)
      - Letters to editor, February 1989 (Box 14, Folder 28)
      - Letters to editor, March 1989 (Box 14, Folder 29)
      - Letters to editor, April 1989 (Box 14, Folder 30)
      - Letters to editor, May 1989-June 1989 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Box 15: Letters to editor, outgoing correspondence
      - Letters to editor, July 1989-August 1989 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Letters to editor, September 1989 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Letters to editor, October 1989-December 1989 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Letters to editor - n.d. (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Outgoing correspondence, July 17, 1981-July 20, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Outgoing correspondence, July 21, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Outgoing correspondence, July 22, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Outgoing correspondence, July 23, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Outgoing correspondence, August 1981-September 1981 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Outgoing correspondence, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Outgoing correspondence, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Outgoing correspondence, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Outgoing correspondence, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Outgoing correspondence, January 1986-March 1986 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Outgoing correspondence, May 1986-July 1986 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - Outgoing correspondence, August 1986; n.d. [1986] (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - Outgoing correspondence, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - Outgoing correspondence, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - Outgoing correspondence, January 3, 1989-January 4, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 19)